Joseph C. Mele collection of dialect recordings from the University of South Alabama
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Joseph C. Mele collection of dialect recordings from the University of South Alabama 1975-1980
AFC 2018/004
346 items.
sound recordings: 346 sound cassettes (C-60): analog.
manuscripts: 1 folder (17 pages)
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of audio recordings of American English dialects from the University of South Alabama, Doy Leale McCall Rare Book & Manuscript Library's Dialect Tape Center collection created by Professor Joseph C. Mele, a former faculty member, between 1975-1980. The collection includes 346 audiocassettes of 30-minute dialect samples recorded by Mele and other recordists (agents) of individuals in 31 states, as well as 42 recordings of English spoken by non-Americans from 23 different countries. Samples generally consist of two parts: an impromptu monologue and a 44-sentence sequence highlighting each English phoneme.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Mele, Joseph C.
Organizations
University of South Alabama.
Subjects
English language--Dialects--Research--United States.; English language--Dialects--Southern States.; English language--Dialects--United States.; English language--Dialects.; Language surveys--United States.
Places
Mobile (Ala.)
Titles
University of South Alabama Dialect Tape Center collection
Form/Genre
Field recordings.; Interviews (Sound recordings); Language surveys.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by state in the United States, and then by city, county, or region; then alphabetically by non-U.S. countries. The identification codes were assigned by Joseph Mele: the first two letters are state abbrevations; the following two letters are the race/ethnicity of the interviewee (most often black or caucasian) and their gender; and the numbers are the year the interview was conducted, followed by the birth year of the interviewee in parentheses. Original order and numbering were maintained. The original collection guide from the Dialect Tape Center at the University of South Alabama is included in the collection. The collection is organized into the following series and subseries: Series 1. Dialect recordings by geographic area; subseries 1. United States spoken English. Subseries 2. International spoken English.
Acquisition
University of South Alabama, Doy Leale McCall Rare Book & Manuscript Library; Donation; 2017.
Related Material
Center for Applied Linguistics collection (AFC 1986/022). The majority of this collection is available online, including recordings made by Joseph Mele for the University of South Alabama: http://www.loc.gov/collections/american-english-dialect-recordings-from-the-center-for-applied-linguistics/?q=mele
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research; access to collection materials may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Biographical Note
Joseph Charles Mele was born in Hammond, Louisiana. He was a graduate of Louisiana State University, where he received a doctorate focusing on communication arts. During his career, he held positions at Louisiana State University, University of Alabama, University of Louisiana-Lafayette, and University of South Alabama where he spent 27 years as professor of speech, speech pathology, audiology, and drama. He died January 12, 2018, in Mobile, Alabama, at the age of 85.
Scope and Content
Audio recordings of American English dialects from the University of South Alabama, Doy Leale McCall Rare Book & Manuscript Library's Dialect Tape Center collection created by Joseph C. Mele, a former faculty member, between 1975-1980. The collection includes 305 audiocassettes of 30-minute dialect samples recorded by Mele and other recordists (agents) of individuals in 31 states, particularly in the South, with more numerous recordings made in Alabama, Tennessee, North Carolina, Virginia, Louisiana, Arkansas, and Missouri. In addition, 41 recordings were made of English spoken by non-Americans from 23 different countries in Asia, Europe, and Australia, as well as in Mexico, Panama, and Nigeria. The birth year of each speaker is documented and ranges from the 1890s to 1950s. Samples generally consist of two parts: an impromtu monologue and a 44-sentence sequence highlighting each English phoneme.
Container List
- Series 1. Dialect recordings by geographic area, 1975-1980
  The collection is arranged alphabetically by state, and then by city, county, or region; then alphabetically by non-U.S. countries. The identification codes were assigned by Joseph Mele: the first two letters are state abbrevations; the following two letters are the race/ethnicity of the interviewee (most often black or caucasian) and their gender; and the numbers are the year the interview was conducted, followed by the birth year of the intervieweee in parentheses. Original order and numbering was maintained. Interviews were conducted by Joseph C. Mele, as well as other linguists and recordists, described as agents.
  - Subseries 1. United States spoken English, 1975-1980
    - Joseph C. Mele collection inventory, 1 folder (Container 1)
      17-page description of the collection from the University of South Alabama Dialect Tape Center, and inventory of tapes, organized alphabetically by state or country.
    - Alabama: Baldwin County, January 11, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR001; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Truda Weekley, birthdate: May 30, 1904. ALCF77 (1904). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Baldwin County, November 5, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR002; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Diane Hartley, birthdate: September 30, 1953. ALCF (1953). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Barbour County, June 10, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR003; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Burmah La Budde, birthdate: December 2, 1919. ALCF77 (1919). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Bayou La Batre, April 22, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR004; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Frances McCullough, birthdate: March 20, 1923. ALCF79 (1923). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Bayou La Batre, April 7, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR005; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Bertha Bosarge, birthdate: September 7, 1931. ALCF79 (1931). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Bayou La Batre, April 15, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR006; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Arthur W. McRay, birthdate: November 9, 1937. ALCM79 (1937). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Bayou La Batre, April 22, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR007; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Richard Gazzier, birthdate: 1947. ALCM79 (1947). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Bayou La Batre, April 15, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR008; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Vera V. Bosarge, birthdate: January 23, 1957. ALCF79 (1957). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Bessemer, June 29, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR009; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ashley Nolan, birthdate: March 23, 1896. ALCM78 (1896). Agent: JoAnn Kierce.
    - Alabama: Bessemer, January 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR010; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      George Randall, birthdate: April 1, 1899. ALCM76 (1899). Agent: JoAnn Kierce.
    - Alabama: Bessemer, June 28, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR011; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Gerald F. Wilkes, birthdate: August 9, 1920. ALCM78 (1920). Agent: JoAnn Kierce.
    - Alabama: Brooklyn, June 1, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR012; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Annie Deloris Caro Faulk, birthdate: January 20, 1894. ALCF76 (1894). Agent: Dr. R.P. Clark.
    - Alabama: Bullock County, June 7, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR013; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John Clarence Blue, birthdate: January 15, 1906. ALCM77 (1906). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Butler County, April 21, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR014; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Bertha Presley, birthdate: May 23, 1935. ALBF79 (1925). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Butler County, June 2, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR015; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ervin Cates, birthdate: September 18, 1929. ALCM77 (1929). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Choctaw County, July 5, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR016; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Minnie Ridgeway, birthdate: December 6, 1918. ALBF78 (1918). Agent: JoAnne Kierce.
    - Alabama: Clark County, October 8, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR017; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Gladys V. Johnson, birthdate: October 1, 1912. ALBF78 (1912). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Coden, April 15, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR018; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Daniel J. Bosarge, birthdate: September 13, 1956. ALCM79 (1956). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Covington County, June 6, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR019; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      George M. Hartin, birthdate: June 5, 1912. ALCM77 (1912). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Crenshaw County, June 5, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR020; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Neil Tarver, birthdate: December 25, 1921. ALCF77 (1921). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Dallas County, May 31, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR021; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Carl C. Cooper, birthdate: July 5, 1908. ALCM76 (1908). Agent: Dr. R.P. Clark.
    - Alabama: Dothan, May 20, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR022; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jack Cox, birthdate: July 26, 1921. ALCM78 (1921). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Elmore County, June 6, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR023; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Bygie Moncrief, birthdate: December 24, 1915. ALCM77 (1915). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Elmore County, June 1, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR024; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edward Sullivan, birthdate: January 1, 1924. ALCM76 (1924). Agent: R.P. Clark.
    - Alabama: Fairhope, February 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR025; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Vashti Thomas, birthdate: September 26, 1912. ALBF79 (1912).
    - Alabama: Geneva, May 28, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR026; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Dorinda Driggers, birthdate: September 23, 1899. ALCF77 (1899). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Greensboro, June 17, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR027; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Margaret Hobson, birthdate, 1890s. ALCF77 (ca. 1890s). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Hartford, May 20, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR028; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mary Cox, birthdate: October 10, 1926. ALCF78 (1926). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: LaFayette, October 22, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR029; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Willie E. Kimbrough, birthdate, January 12, 1902. ALBF79 (1902). Agent: B. Loganbill.
    - Alabama: Mobile, September 17, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR030; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edith M. Murphy, birthdate: November 3, 1885. ALCF75 (1885). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, September 17, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR031; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Martin L. Horst, birthdate: June 25, 1897. ALCM75 (1897). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, July 19, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR032; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      "J," F, birthdate: January 9, 1899. ALBF77 (ca. 1899). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, July 28, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR033; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      "A" (name withheld), birthdate: August 27, 1900. ALBM77 (1900). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, August 8, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR034; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mattie Lancaster, birthdate: August 12, 1905. ALCF77 (1905). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, July 28, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR035; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      "B" (name withheld), birthdate: April 7, 1907. ALBM77 (1907). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, June 23, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR036; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Julian Rayford, birthdate: April 7, 1908. ALCM77 (1908). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, June 28, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR037; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Louise Wiggins, birthdate: August 4, 1913. ALCF77 (1913). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, December 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR038; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nora Odom, birthdate: August 22, 1913. ALCF76 (1913). Agent, Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, June 29, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR039; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Cedric Woodruff, birthdate: January 7, 1919. ALCM77 (1919). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, June 22, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR040; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Earlie Mae Hines, birthdate: April 4, 1926. ALBF77 (1926). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, July 13, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR041; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mary M. Blackburn, birthdate: April 17, 1927. ALCF79 (1927). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, February 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR042; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Blanche Williams, birthdate: February 4, 1932. ALBF79 (1932). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, June 22, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR043; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Oscar Mae Hines, birthdate: December 4, 1955. ALBF77 (1955). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, November 27, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR044; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Cassandra M. Saffo, birthdate: January 21, 1960. ALBF78 (1960). Agent, Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Mobile, June 3, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR045; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Wash Hill, birthdate: 1890s. ALBM77 (ca. 1890). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Montgomery, June 7, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR046; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John Eva Johnson, birthdate: March 19, 1911. ALBF77 (1911). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Montgomery, June 3, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR047; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Clyde Annette Myrick, birthdate: September 13, 1916. ALCF77 (1916). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Montgomery, June 3, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR048; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mamie Davis, birthdate: December 20. 1920. ALBF77 (1920). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Montgomery, April 22, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR049; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Marcelle G. Luigle, birthdate: February 12, 1923. ALCF (1923). Agent, Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Montgomery, June 1, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR050; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Annette Baxter, birthdate: June 3, 1927. ALCF77 (1927). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Montgomery, May 29, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR051; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John Hamilton Dorrill, birthdate: April 27, 1929. ALCM77 (1929). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Opelika, June 6, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR052; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Vinie Sexton Thomas, birthdate: August 16, 1921. ALCF77 (1921). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Opp, March 7, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR053; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sarah H. Bembow, birthdate: July 1, 1918. ALCF79 (1918). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Opp, June 6, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR054; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Carolyn Watson, birthdate: February 26, 1930. ALCF77 (1930). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Perry County, May 28, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR055; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Elvira Bledsoe Frith, birthdate: October 5, 1923. ALCF76 (1923). Agent: R.P. Clark.
    - Alabama: Pike County, June 6, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR056; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ethel Mitcham, birthdate: January 27, 1898. ALCF77 (1898). Agent: Roy Clark.
    - Alabama: Selma, November 2, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR057; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mary Murray, birthdate: July 30, 1910. ALCF77 (1910). Agent: JoAnne Kierce.
    - Alabama: Stockton, June 22, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR058; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Annie Myles, birthdate: December 11, 1922. ALBF77 (1922). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Alabama: Troy, September 17, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR059; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lamona Lucas, birthdate: November 25, 1934. ALCF75 (1934). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Arkansas: Ashley County, October 5, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR060; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Connie Lee High, birthdate: August 25, 1958. ARCF77 (1958). Agent: Harvey S. Spicer.
    - Arkansas: Cross County, April 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR061; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Kathy Pitts, birthdate: August 16, 1956. ARCF76 (1956). Agent: Harvey S. Spicer.
    - Arkansas: Drew County, April 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR062; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Michael Lee Qualls, birthdate: January 16, 1956. ARCM76 (1956). Agent: Harvey S. Spicer.
    - Arkansas: Franklin County, April 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR063; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Shirley Bell, birthdate: October 23, 1931. ARCF76 (1931). Agent: Harvey S. Spicer.
    - Arkansas: Garland County, April 23, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR064; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Andrew S. Sharp, birthdate: August 1, 1902. ARCM (1902). Agent: D.T. Garnett.
    - Arkansas: Hawes, May 1, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR065; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lillie E. McGrew, birthdate: March 10, 1898. ARCF76 (1898). Agent: Dr. T. Garnett.
    - Arkansas: Hawes, May 2, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR066; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Marie T. Lavendar, birthdate: June 26, 1910. ARCF76 (1910). Agent: D.T. Garnett.
    - Arkansas: Hot Springs, May 4, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR067; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Louis Mary Wilhite, birthdate: April 13, 1915. ARCF76 (1915). Agent: D.T. Garnett.
    - Arkansas: Lawrence County, March 22, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR068; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sherrill Fagan, birthdate: January 11, 1942. ARCM76 (1942). Agent: Giles Zimmer.
    - Arkansas: Oden, April 22, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR069; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Robert Zelma Whilhite, birthdate: 1909. ARCM76 (1909). Agent: D.T. Garnett.
    - Arkansas: Northwest Arkansas, August 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR070; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Rip Lindsay, birthdate: July 10, 1918. ARCM76 (1918). Agent: Mary Ingalls.
    - Arkansas: Southeast Arkansas, April 13, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR071; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      William R. Bell, birthdate: December 7, 1925. ARCM75 (1925). Agent: Harvey S. Spicer.
    - Arkansas: Southeast Arkansas, April 15, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR072; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen B. Wilcoxon, birthdate: March 4, 1929. ARCF76 (1929). Agent: Harvey S. Spicer.
    - Colorado: Denver, March 31, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR073; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ruth Wheeler, birthdate: June 20, 1888. COCF77 (1888). Agent: Mary Alice Minderhout.
    - Colorado: area unknown, March 29, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR074; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Earl P. Miller, birthdate: March 7, 1925. COCM76 (1925). Agent: Giles Zimmer.
    - Colorado: Groveport (Central), December 6, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR075; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jean Parker, birthdate: January 23, 1925. COCF79 (1925). Agent: Jean Luere.
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport, March 13, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR076; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Richard A. Greiser, birthdate: October 2, 1907. CTCM77 (1907). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport, December, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR077; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Wheeler H. Silliman, birthdate: 1909. CTCM77 (1909). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport, October 30, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR078; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Andrew J. Oros, birthdate: March 27, 1910. CTCM77 (1910). Agent: Daigle.
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport, December 7, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR079; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Aaron Abramson, birthdate: 1920. CTCM77 (1920). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport, December 14, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR080; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Irene M. Andrejko, birthdate: December 23, 1929. CTCF77 (1929). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport, December 9, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR081; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Frederick Haydon, birthdate: April 11, 1934. CTCM77 (1934). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Bridgeport, December 7, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR082; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Carol Adzima, birthdate: October 14, 1938. CTCF77 (1938). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Darien, March 13, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR083; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Harold Dart, birthdate: July 4, 1907. CTCM77 (1907). Agent: Richard Daigle.
    - Connecticut: Easton, December 8, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR084; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Clifford Gillette, birthdate: November 10, 1888. CTCM77 (1888). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Easton, December 5, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR085; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Benjamin Silverman, birthdate: 1898. CTHM77 (1898).
    - Connecticut: Easton, December 5, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR086; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      William Snow, birthdate: 1905. CTCM77 (1905). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Fairfield, December 9, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR087; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Karen Hayden, birthdate: January 16, 1941. CTCF77 (1941). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Mossup, March 28, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR088; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Anna Maria Hebert, birthdate: September 22, 1903. CTCF76 (1903). Agent: D. Parker.
    - Connecticut: Norwich, December 16, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR089; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Chris L. Sinagulia, birthdate: May 14, 1931. CTCF77 (1931). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Connecticut: Trumbull, December 8, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR090; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Betty Rohr, birthdate: June 21, 1925. CTCF77 (1925). Agent: Dr. Patricia Jenkins.
    - Florida: Escambia County, May 25, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR091; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen Manry, birthdate: June 26, 1958. FLCF78 (1958). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Florida: Tallahassee, August 3, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR092; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Barbara Jensen, birthdate: June 5, 1948. FLCF78 (1948). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Georgia: Savannah, November 10, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR093; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mr. Max Lipsitz, birthdate: April 27, 1905. GAHM75 (1905). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Illinois: Chicago, September 30, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR094; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Lillian Quinn, birthdate: April 26, 1898. ILCF79 (1898). Agent: Dr. B. Quinn.
    - Indiana: Evansville, December 14, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR095; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Susan Pica, birthdate: April 4, 1960. INCF76 (1960). Agent: Sheri Sinmerman [tentative spelling].
    - Indiana: St. Joseph County, February 7, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR096; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mark M. Kline, birthdate: March 21, 1907. INCM78 (1907). Agent: C. A. Shoupe.
    - Indiana: Topeka, January 9, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR097; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Orvin Kaufman, birthdate: April 23, 1916. INCM77 (1916). Agent: Craig Hosterman.
    - Kansas: Barkley, November 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR098; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ray E. Shirley, birthdate: September 26, 1929. KSCM79 (1929).
    - Kentucky: Daviess County, March 16, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR099; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nellie Grady, birthdate: November 2, 1909. KYCF79 (1909). Agent: M. Myers.
    - Kentucky: Elkton, March 18, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR100; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ms. Agnes S. Harralson, birthdate: September 21, 1921. KYCF79 (1896). Agent: Marshall Myers.
    - Kentucky: Whitesburg, August 18, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR101; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Annis Blair Franklin, birthdate: August 11, 1899. KYCF75 (1899). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Louisiana: Acadian area, April 10, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR102; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lowis LeBanc, birthdate: July 1, 1908. LACM77 (1908). Agent: Steven Cooper.
    - Louisiana: Acadian area, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR103; 1 sound cassette: analog.